Hello Hello Friends Welcome to Your Gallery
Express Express to Your Wealth Creation
Friends, today in this video I am going to
talk about two stocks, I even
think that both of you will have
these stocks in your portfolio. Along with this,
friends, I want to tell you
that I am
not going to sell you any advance by talking about The Best of, so
friends, let's start by
quickly checking these parameters.
First of all, the company is
Reliance Industries Limited, India's number
one company, I am going to share some detailed
information about it with you.
Before that, I would
request you that if you are new to this channel, then
please subscribe to this channel
and also press the notification bell icon
so that you keep getting updates of such informative videos from
time to time. So here
friends, you should know that the valuation of Reliance's
subsidiary company Jio Platform
Care is being calculated at a
value of ₹1600 crore
and right now the total investment has
come into this platform.  There is
some news going on in the market that
Microsoft is going to
buy another 2.5 percent stake in the Jio platform and
along with this, friends, the Jio platform is preparing to list on America's leading
technology index Nasdaq in the
form of a bank IPO, so keep this in mind as well.
Along with this, I
believe that there are many benefits. If this Jio
platform gets listed on Nasdaq, then the
elevation of the Jio platform will give it a
value of hundred million dollars. So
keeping all these things in mind, as far as I feel,
friends, if your platform gets such a
great start, the parent company of this platform,
Reliance Industries
Limited, is sure to face tremendous opposition
in the coming time. So, I
wanted to share this information with you. Along with this,
friends, the next company is
Hindustan Unilever Limited Natural, it is the
number one company in the family G sector of India.
I even feel that
friends, this is a mighty generation stock. Here,
you should look at these two legs, the
actual
president of Jio is a tremendous person.  There
is brand value in the market and along with this,
friends, whether the distribution is rich or not, retail
and shopkeepers or even the smallest shops have
that level with their products,
so you should know friends
that Hindustan Unilever has customer rich,
our population in India
is above 130 crore, out of this more than 70 thousand crore
people use their products,
along with this, friends, I am going to share a great deal that
this is a debt-free company, so I am going to quickly
share some products with you,
you should check these products,
you must be using one or the other of these products in your home, so keeping all these
parameters in mind, friends, as
far as I am concerned,
I see a tremendous potential in these two companies
in the future, otherwise this is my
address system, I can also be wrong here,
you should not follow this thing blindly,
if you want to make any investment,
you can
consult a channel advisor on these two stars and you
can ask a question, so friends, thank
you very much for watching this video.  If
you like this video please subscribe
to my channel and hit the bell icon and see you in the
next video Jai Hind